<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.scanlite.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+ and GFDL-1.3</project_license>
  <name>Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Skanlite</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxSkanlitexx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Skanlite</name>
  <summary>Image Scanning Application</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Aplicació per a la digitalització d'imatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Aplicació per a la digitalització d'imatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Aplikace pro skenování obrázků</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Anwendung zum Scannen von Bildern</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Image Scanning Application</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Aplicación para escanear imágenes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Applicazione per la scansione delle immagini</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Afbeeldingscanprogramma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Program do skanowania obrazów</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Aplicação de Digitalização de Imagens</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Aplikácia na skenovanie obrázkov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Bildinläsningsprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Resim Tarama Uygulaması</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для сканування зображень</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxImage Scanning Applicationxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
   Skanlite is a simple image scanning application to scan and save images.
   Skanlite is based on libksane, an interface for SANE library to control image scanners.
  </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Skanlite és una senzilla aplicació per escanejar imatges i desar-les. Skanlite es basa en «libsane», una interfície per a la biblioteca SANE que controla els escàners d'imatges.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Skanlite és una senzilla aplicació per escanejar imatges i guardar-les. Skanlite es basa en «libsane», una interfície per a la biblioteca SANE que controla els escàners d'imatges.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Skanlite is a simple image scanning application to scan and save images. Skanlite is based on libksane, an interface for SANE library to control image scanners.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Skanlite es una sencilla aplicación para escanear y guardar imágenes. Skanlite se basa en libksane, una interfaz para la biblioteca SANE que permite controlar escáneres.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Skanlite è una semplice applicazione per la scansione e il salvataggio delle immagini. Skanlite si basa su libksane, un'interfaccia per la libreria SANE per il controllo degli scanner per immagini.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Skanlite is eenvoudige toepassing voor het scannen en opslaan van afbeeldingen. Skanlite is gebaseerd op libksane, een interface voor de SANE-bibliotheek voor de besturing van afbeeldingsscanners.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Skanlite jest prostą aplikacją do skanowania i zapisywania obrazów. Skanlite jest oparty na libksane, interfejsie dla biblioteki SANE do obsługi skanerów obrazów.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Skanlite é uma aplicação simples de digitalização de imagens para digitalizar e gravar as imagens. O Skanlite baseia-se na 'libksane', uma interface para a biblioteca SANE que controla os 'scanners' de imagens.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Skanlite är ett enkelt bildläsningsprogram för att läsa in och spara bilder.Skanlite är baserat på libksane, ett gränssnitt till SANE-biblioteket som styr bildläsare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Skanlite, resim taramak ve kaydetmek için basit bir tarama uygulamasıdır. Skanlite, resim tarayıcılarını denetlemekte kullanılan SANE kütüphanesi olan libksane tabanlıdır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Skanlite — проста програма для сканування зображень і збереження даних зображень до файлів. Роботу Skanlite засновано на бібліотеці libksane, інтерфейсі до бібліотек SANE для керування сканерами зображень.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxSkanlite is a simple image scanning application to scan and save images. Skanlite is based on libksane, an interface for SANE library to control image scanners.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Recursos:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Özellikleri:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Save dialog for every image scanned or saving the images immediately in a specified folder with auto-generated names and format</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Diàleg per desar cada imatge escanejada o desar les imatges immediatament en una carpeta especificada amb noms i format generats automàticament</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Diàleg per guardar cada imatge escanejada o guardar les imatges immediatament en una carpeta especificada amb noms i format generats automàticament</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Save dialog for every image scanned or saving the images immediately in a specified folder with auto-generated names and format</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Diálogo para guardar las imágenes escaneadas o para guardarlas inmediatamente en la carpeta indicada con nombres generados automáticamente y en el formato indicado.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Finestra di dialogo per ogni scansione immagine o salvataggio immediato delle immagini in una cartella specifica con nomi e formati generati in automatico</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">De dialoog voor opslaan van elke gescande afbeelding of het onmiddellijk in een een gespecificeerde map opslaan met automatisch gegenereerde namen en formaten.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Okno dialogowe zapisywania dla każdego zeskanowanego obrazu lub zapisywanie obrazów bezpośrednio w podanym katalogu z samodzielnie utworzonymi nazwami i wybranym formatem</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Janela de gravação para todas as imagens digitalizadas ou gravação imediata das imagens numa pasta à escolha, com nomes e formato gerados automaticamente</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Dialog för att spara varje bild som läses in, eller spara bilderna omedelbart i en angiven katalog med automatiskt genererade namn och format</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Her taranan resim için kaydetme penceresi ya da otomatik isim ve biçim oluşturma ile belirtilen klasöre anında kaydetme.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість показу діалогового вікна збереження для кожного з зображень та можливість автоматичного зберігання зображень із автоматично визначеною назвою до вказаної теки.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSave dialog for every image scanned or saving the images immediately in a specified folder with auto-generated names and formatxx</li>
      <li>Support for networks scanners</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Implementació per a escàners en xarxa</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Implementació per a escàners en xarxa</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für Netzwerk-Scanner</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Support for networks scanners</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite el uso de escáneres en red.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per scanner di rete</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor scanners in het netwerk</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa skanerów w sieci</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para 'scanners' na rede</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för nätverksbildläsare</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Ağ tarayıcı desteği</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка роботи зі сканерами з мережі.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for networks scannersxx</li>
      <li>Preview with selection feature for the final scan</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Vista prèvia amb la característica de selecció per a l'escaneig final</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista prèvia amb la característica de selecció per a l'escaneig final</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Preview with selection feature for the final scan</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Vista previa con función de selección para el escaneo final.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Anteprima con funzionalità di selezione per la scansione finale</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Voorbeeldweergave met geselecteerde functie voor de uiteindelijke scan</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Podgląd z możliwością zaznaczenia ostatecznego skanowania</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Antevisão com funcionalidade de selecção para a digitalização final</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Förhandsgranskning med markeringsfunktion för slutlig bild</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Son tarama için seçim özelliği ile önizleme</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Засіб попереднього перегляду із можливістю вибору остаточної області сканування.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPreview with selection feature for the final scanxx</li>
      <li>Scanning multiple selections of an image</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Escaneig de múltiples seleccions d'una imatge</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Escaneig de múltiples seleccions d'una imatge</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Sannen mehrerer Bereiche eines Fotos</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Scanning multiple selections of an image</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Escanear múltiples selecciones de una imagen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Selezioni multiple di scansione di un'immagine</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Scannen van meerdere selecties van een afbeelding</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Skanowanie wielu obszarów obrazu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Digitalização de várias selecções numa imagem</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Läs in flera markeringar i en bild</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Bir resimde birden çok seçimi tarama</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість одночасного сканування декількох позначених областей на зображенні.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxScanning multiple selections of an imagexx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.kde.org/images/screenshots/skanlite.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org/applications/graphics/skanlite/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=skanlite</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>skanlite</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
